Guide to the Douglas Menuez Photography Collection MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 5. Accessions 2006-207 and 2007-081, 54.75 Linear feet
  - Subseries 1. Jobs
    - Instinet, binder 2 (4 folders), 1994 (Box-folder 7-12, Box-folder 8-3)
      Note: The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls, labeled “CD makeup”: 88380, frames 7-12, 25-36; 88381, frames 2-7; 88382, frames 13-18; 88383, frames 25-30; 88386, frames 14-19, 26-31; 88387, frames 25-30; 88388, frames 6-12; 88390, frames 34-36; 88396, frames 1-5; 88403, frames 25-30, 34-36; 88405, frames 13-18, 88406, frames 19-30; 88464, frames 1-6, 13-24, 31-35; 88466, frames 1-6; 88468, frames 1-6, 13-18; 88469, frames 1-6, 19-24; 88470, frames 13-18, 25-30; 88471, frames 18-30; 88484, frames 7-12; 88639, frames 34-36; 88640, frames 19-24. Roll 88392 is incomplete, negatives 7-12 are missing, labeled “IU ’97 Portfolio”. Roll 88473 is incomplete, negatives 7-12 are missing 88463 is incomplete, negatives 25-30 are missing.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 35 Folder 16 and Flat Box 36 Folders 1-3 for negatives.
    - Kaleida, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Contains 636 black and white images; Rolls: 81311-81320, 88448-88456.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 36 Folders 4-5 for negatives.
    - Kodak APCL, 1993 (Box 8, Folders 5-7)
      Number of color images unspecified: no corresponding negatives; Rolls: 1-20, 22-28, 30-46, 48-50, 6845-6852, 6854-6856, 6863.
      Note attached: "when film is returned please contact Connie Latch 922-1890."
    - Kodak Developers Conference, 1992 (Box 8, Folders 8-11)
      Contains 1,080 color images; Rolls: K1-K24, K26, K28-K31, K33-K69, K71-K84.
      Note: there are no contact sheets for the following rolls: K25, K27, K32, K70, 190. There are no negatives for rolls K3, K6, K16, K74.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 36 Folders 6-13 for negatives.
    - Kodak, binder 1, 1991 (Box 8, Folders 12-13)
      Contains 1,296 black and white, and color images; Rolls: 10003, 10004, 68159-68195.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 68180.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 36 Folders 14-17 for negatives.
    - Kodak, binder 2, 1991 (Box 9, Folders 1-2)
      Contains 1,080 black and white images; Rolls: 68195-68224.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 68221. See Subseries 3, Flat Box 37 Folders 1-3 for negatives.
    - LEK/Alcar, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Contains 612 black and white images; Rolls: 85603-85619.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 37 Folders 4-5 for negatives.
    - Lightsource, binder 1, 1991 (Box 9, Folders 4-6)
      Contains 1,100 black and white images; Rolls: 9504, 9508-9517, 9532-9534, 66556-66562, 66841-66846, 66886-66893, 67156, 68158-67163, 67486-67495, 71326-71329, 9417-9419, 9447.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 9417-9419, 9447. See Subseries 3, Flat Box 37 Folders 6-11 for negatives.
    - Lightsource, binder 2, 1991 (Box 9, Folders 7-10)
      Contains 1,300 black and white images; Rolls: 9351-9365, 9367-9369, 9381-9396, 9417-9419, 9423-9450, 9473-9476, 9491-9499, 75520. Persons depicted: David Sosna, et.al.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 9494. There are no contact sheets for the following roll: 9366.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 37 Folders 12-19 for negatives.
    - Linc Quantum Analytics (2 folders), 1995 (Box-folder 9-11, Box-folder 10-1)
      Contains 1, 476 black and white images; Rolls: 63459-63483, 70934-70946, 70965-70974.
      Note: there are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 63463, 63467, 63472, 63480.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 37 Folder 20 and Flat Box 38 Folders 1-5 for negatives.
    - Mac Week, editorial, 1991 (Box 10, Folders 2-4)
      Contains 1,930 black and white images; Rolls: 69070-69103, 69105-69107, 69403, 69404, 69406, 70412-70422.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 69082. See Subseries 3, Flat Box 38 Folders 6-11 for negatives.
    - Mac World Anniversary, editorial, 1994 (Box 10, Folders 5-6)
      Contains 220 black and white images; Rolls: 76186-76193, 76329-76345.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 38 Folders 12-16 for negatives.
    - Mac World Anniversary, editorial, 1993 (Box 10, Folders 8-9)
      Contains 400 2.25 black and white images; Rolls: 85041-85053, 85361-85369, 0800-0814, 75974-75979.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 38 Folder 18 to Flat Box 39 Folder 5 for negatives.
    - Mac World, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      615 black and white images; Rolls: 92308-92323.
      Note: there are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 22436-22448.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 39 Folders 6-9 for negatives.
    - Mac World, editorial, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Contains 360 black and white images; Rolls: 61238-61247.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 38 Folder 17 for negatives.
    - Misc. Tech (2 folders) (Box-folder 10-11, Box-folder 11-1)
      General note
      Notes attached: "Broderbund Rolls 1509-1527 is a 'buy-out'; we will not have the negatives"; "CKS 162"; "Coblentz sheets only"; "Lucent 16"; "Robert Noyce; Tech Museum San Jose"; "Planet Project only negatives".
      Contains 216 mixed frames; Rolls: 1504-1522, 1524-1527 (Broderbund), 78470-78474 (CKS), 91691-91694, 91697-91704 (Coblentz), 41919 (>Lucent), 64497-64511 (Planet Project), 03767-03775 (Westfield). Slides 6040-32C – 6040-32E (Robert Noyce). Companies noted: Broderbund, CKS, Coblentz, Lucent, Robert Noyce, Planet Project, Westfield.
      Note: there are no negatives for 1504-1522, 1524-1527, 91691-91694, 91697-91704, 64497-64511, 03767-03775. See Subseries 3, Flat Box 39 Folder 10 for negatives.
    - Mitchell Hutchins, 1994 (Box 11, Folders 2-4)
      Contains 2,100 color images; Rolls: 503-532, 535-566. Note: there are no negatives for roll 566.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 39 Folders 11-16 for negatives.
    - NetFrame, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Contains 396 black and white images; Rolls: 66382-66392, 68470-68472, 66449, 66450.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 39 Folders 17-18 for negatives.
    - NetFrame, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Contains 726 black and white images; Rolls: 98489-98498, 103733-103745.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 39 Folders 19-20 for negatives.
    - NetFrame, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Contains 528 black and white images; Rolls: 01122-01137.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 40 Folders 1-2 for negatives.
    - NetObjects, 1996 (Box 11, Folders 8-9)
      Contains 1,155 black and white images; Rolls: 0049, 0051, 0052, 0055, 0057, 0059, 0061, 0063, 0065, 0066, 0068, 95981-95983, 00275-00281, 00314-00319, 08141-08146, 00999-01007.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 40 Folders 3-6 for negatives.
    - NetObjects, 1996 April (Box 24, Folders 7-8)
      Rolls: 01613-01624, 01725-1736, 2077-2082, 02132, 01960-01968. Note: 2077 is incomplete; frames 12-18 are missing; note attached: "Sent to Master Portfolio ’98."
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 49 Folders 5-10 for negatives.
    - NetObjects, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Contains 667 black and white images; Rolls: 23180-23193, Slide: 9947.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 40 Folders 7-8 for negatives.
    - NetObjects, employees, 1998 (Box 11, Folders 11-12)
      Contains 540 black and white images; Rolls: 42802-42824.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 40 Folders 9-11 for negatives.
    - NetObjects, 1999 (Box 77, Folders 1-4)
      Rolls: 69205-69232.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 40 Folders 12-15 for negatives.
    - Netscape ReVerb, 1997 (Box 12, Folders 2-3)
      Contains 938 black and white images; Rolls: 21840-21869, 22981-22984.
      Person depicted: James Barksdale, et. al.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 40 Folders 16-19 for negatives.
    - Pixar, 1996 (Box 12, Folders 4-5)
      Contains 900 black and white images; Rolls: 00954-00971, 07835-07843.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 00962, 07838, 07842.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 40 Folder 20 to Flat Box 41 Folder 2 for negatives.
    - Planet Project, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Contains 400 color images; Rolls: 64497-64511. Note: contains letter from company regarding photographs taken.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 41 Folders 3-4 for negatives.
    - QVC, 1994 (Box-folder 12-7, Box-folder 13-2)
      Contains 7,500 mixed images; Rolls: 76620, 76621, 76641-76652, 75959-75965, 45684-45689, 1176-1182, 1191-1199, 1083-1088, 1090-1096A, 77018-77053, 1108-1112, 1246-1253, 46402-46421, 46423, 1095-1107, 77133-77136, 77143-77152, 77154, 77155, 45508-45517, 45683.
      Persons depicted: Stephen Chao, et.al.
      Note: The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls, labeled “CD makeup”: 76620, frames 19-27; 76621, frames 31,32; 76644, frames 7-12; 76645, frames 31-36; 76646, frames 26-30l 76650, frames 1-6; 1181, frames 21-25; 1195, frames 1-11; 1197, frames 36-44, 1; 1198, frames 14-18; 1083, frames 18-21; 1093, frames 26-30; 1095, frames 2-6, 32-36; 1096A, frames 20-23; 77025, frames 19-24; 77026, frames 1-6; 77032, frames 19-24; 77036, frames 19-24; 77047, frames 7-12, 25-30; 77048, frames 7-12, 31-33; 1108, frames 1-5; 1110, frames 16-20, 31-36; 1246, frames 11-15; 1251, frames 35, 36, 36A; 46402, frames 13-18; 46403, frames 13-24; 46405, frames 35, 36, 36A; 46406, frames 34-36; 46407, frames 1-12; 1102, frames 6-10; 77134, frames 25-33; 77151, frames 19-30; 77154, frames 13-18; 45508, frames 1-6; 45514, frames 14-19.
      The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls, labeled “IU ’97 Portfolio”: 1196, frames 2-8; 77135, frames 18-23.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 41 Folders 5-20 for negatives.
    - QVC Network, 1994 (Box 13, Folders 3-5)
      Contains 1,600 black and white images; Rolls: 76951, 76955-76987, 79007-79010, 47005-47008, 1255.
      Note: The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls, labeled “CD makeup”: 76957, frames 25-30; 76959, frames 18-30; 76960, frames 19-24; 76961, frames 13-19, 25-30; 76962, frames 7-12; 76965, frames 19-24; 76970, frames 7-12, 25-30, 35, 36; 76971, frames 31-34; 76976, frames 7-12; 76987, frames 13-18; 79007, frames 8-12; 1257, frames 6-10.
      The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls, labeled “IU ’97 Portfolio”: 76975, frames 25-30.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 42 Folders 1-5 for negatives.
    - Robert Stephens Broom & Broom, 1996 (Box 13, Folders 6-7)
      Contains 666 mixed images; Rolls: 00132-00151, 00621, 00622-00632, 014, 45378, 45380, unlabeled. Note: there are no negatives for rolls: 014, 45378, 45380, unlabeled.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 42 Folders 6-9 for negatives.
    - Robertson Stephens, Tri Net, 1995 (Box 13, Folders 8-11)
      Contains 2,087 mixed images; Rolls: 10131-10165, 10064-10080, 001-015, 45375-45379, 45594.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 10152-10165. There are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 45380, unlabeled. Note attached: "Elizabeth Drukker at Trinet has all portrait negatives, 5/10/96" (on contact sheet 10152).
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 42 Folders 10-17 for negatives.
    - Saffo, Paul, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Contains 612 mixed images; Rolls: 9253-9267.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 42 Folders 18-19 for negatives.
    - Sapient, binder 1, 2000 (Box 14, Folders 1-3)
      Contains 720 black and white images; Rolls: 214380-21468, 21513-21549.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 42 Folder 20 to Flat box 43 Folder 5 for negatives.
    - Sapient, binder 2, A Day in the Life, 2000 (Box 14, Folders 4-5)
      Contains 1,200 color images; Rolls: 66601-66622, 66658-66665.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 43 Folders 6-8 for negatives.
    - Sapient, binder 3, 2000 (Box 14, Folders 6-7)
      Contains 1,600 mixed images; Rolls: 66965- 67009.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 43 Folders 9-13 for negatives.
    - SGI, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Contains 720 color images; Rolls: 44712-44729, E1, E2.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 43 Folders 14-15 for negatives.
    - Shoreline Pacific, binder 1, 1996 (Box 14, Folders 9-10)
      Contains 888 black and white images; Rolls: 08005-08014, 91751-91755, 91976, 96261, 96262, 1054-1056. Note: there are no prints for the following rolls: 1050-1053.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 43 Folders 16-18 for negatives.
    - Shoreline Pacific, binder 2, 1996 (Box 14, Folders 11-12)
      Contains 1,044 black and white images; Rolls: 12362-12389.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 43 Folder 19 to Flat Box 44 Folder 1 for negatives.
    - Shoreline Pacific, Bielenberg Design, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      Contains 324 black and white images; Rolls: 16281-16289.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 44 Folder 2 for negatives.
    - Shoreline Pacific, Brochure, binder 1 (2 folders), 1998 (Box-folder 14-14, Box-folder 15-1)
      Contains 972 mixed images; Rolls: 1-7. 42091-42105, 42127, 42128, 47816, 47818, 47827. Note: there are no negatives for rolls 47816, 47818, 47827.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 44 Folders 3-5 for negatives.
    - Shoreline Pacific, binder 2, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Contains 504 black and white images; Rolls: 47815, 47817, 47819-47825, 47828, 47829. Note: there are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 47816, 47818, 47826, 47827.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 44 Folders 6-7 for negatives.
    - Stanford Pub Course (Flat-box 78, Folder 9)
      4 black and white prints
    - Strategic Pacific, binder 1, 1994 (Box 15, Folders 3-4)
      Slides (12 sleeves): contains 35-mm color slides (175).
    - Strategic Pacific, binder 2, 1994 (Box 15, Folders 5-7)
      Slides (22 sleeves): contains 35- mm color slides (360).
    - Strategic Pacific, binder 3, 1994 (Box 15, Folders 8-11)
      Slides (24 sleeves, 3 sheets): contains 35- mm color slides (380).
    - Strategic Pacific, binder 4, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Contains 1,700 mixed images; Rolls: 79370-79374, 79376, 79377, 74149. Note: there are no prints for the following contact sheets: 76774-76785, 76787, 76788 76800, 76801, 79292-79300, 79302, 79303, 21390-21400, 91684-91690.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 44 Folders 8-13 for negatives.
    - Strategic Pacific, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Contains 144 black and white images; Rolls: 100725. There are no prints for the following rolls: 100726-100729.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 44 Folder 14 for negatives.
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 1, 1992 (Box 16, Folders 3-6)
      Contains 1,722 black and white negatives; Rolls: 88192-88220, 88228, 88229, 88237, 88244, 88245, 88247-88249, 88259, 88267, 88272, 88285, 88288, 88292, 88294, 88301, 88311, 88312, 88322-88326, 88328, 88329, 88336, 88343, 88359, 88365, 88367, 88386, 88388-88394.
      Note: the following negatives are missing from their respective rolls: 88196, frames 1-7; 88197, frames 11-16, 23-34; 88200, frames 19-30; 88201, frames 22-27; 88202, frames 7-12, 25-30l 88203, frames 8-19, 32-36; 88204, frames 1-6, 19-24; 88205, frames 7-12; 88206, frames 24-35; 88208, frames 7-12, 31-35; 88209, frames 7-12, 19-24; 88210, frames 1-12, 25-30; 88212, frames 1-6, 12-14; 88214, frames 1-6; 88216, frames 1-6, 25-30; 88220, frames 13-18; 88229, frames 13-18, 25-30; 88237, frames 15-20, 27-32; 88267, frames 1-6, 25-36; 88272, frames 31-34; 88285, frames 31-36; 88292, frames 31-36; 88322, frames 9-15, 28-33; 88325, frames 26-36; 88326, frames 17-23; 88329, frames 24-29; 88388, frames 9-14, 21-26; 88389, frames 4-9; 88390, frames 22-27; 88293, frames 22-27; 88394, frames 1-3, 43, 44.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 44 Folder 15 to Flat Box 45 Folder 1 for negatives.
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 2, 1992 (Box 16, Folders 7-8)
      Additional slides: "Loose leaves in front of binder" (7 sleeves and 13 miscellaneous prints). Note: Slide rolls in binder #2 are scattered throughout the various categories.
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 2, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Slides: Courtney's First Picks (3 sleeves)
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 2, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Slides: Tight Edit (5 sleeves)
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 2, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      Slides: Rough Edit (5 sleeves)
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 2, 1992 (Box 16, Folders 12-13)
      Slides: Sun Microsystems, Computer Bike Outs (13 sleeves)
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 2, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Slides: Sun Microsystems, Roller Blader Outs (9 sleeves)
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 2, 1992 (Box 17, Folders 1-3)
      Slides: Sun Microsystems, Waterfight Outs (22 sleeves)
    - SVN, 1999 (Box 17, Folders 4-6)
      Contains 1,600 black and white images; Rolls: 9299-9317, 9322-9348, 9377. Note: there are no negatives for roll 9377.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 45 Folders 2-6 for negatives.
    - Taligent, 1994 (Box 17, Folders 7-9)
      Contains 1,600 black and white images; Rolls: 76576-76589, 76649, 46678-46704, 78424-78437, 78484-78488.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 45 Folders 7-12 for negatives.
    - TED III, binder 1, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Contain 2,811 color images; Rolls: 1-97, 99, 100, 102-157, 190-192. Note: there are no negatives for rolls 13, 39, 101, 190.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 45 Folder 13 to Flat Box 46 Folder 7 for negatives.
    - TED III, binder 1 continued, 1992 (Box 18, Folders 1-5)
    - Teseract, binder 1, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folders 6-8)
      Contains 2,100 black and white images; Rolls: 94077-94111, 95423-95440.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 46 Folders 8-12 for negatives.
    - Teseract, binder 2, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folders 9-10)
      Contains 2,100 black and white images; Rolls: 96795-96802, 71412-71418, 71420-71422, 88005-88012, 99984-99990, 103097-103106.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 46 Folders 13-16 for negatives.
    - Teseract, binder 3, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folders 11-12)
      Contains 2,100 black and white images; Rolls: 89866-89872, 90205, 90206, 100259-100275, 103534-103538, 103540-103543.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 46 Folders 17-20 for negatives.
    - TFI, 1987 (Box 19, Folders 1-2)
      Contains 6,300 black and white images; Rolls: 074650-074656, 08880, 13148, 13149, 18809-18811, 188650, 23695-23698, 17905, 17906, 30190, 30191, 188650.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 188650. There are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 01120, 01121, 17704, 17902, 17903, 17907, 31385, 25692-25696, 061299.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 47 Folders 1-3 for negatives.
    - TFI, 1988 (Box 19, Folders 3-8)
      Contains 6,300 black and white images; Rolls: 09550, 22200-22203, 22205-22208, 071318-07324, 07326-07328, 07331, 01201-01206, 061227, 061228, 18190-18194, 31370-31379, 31382-31384, 16300-16305, 18101-18106, 15490-15495, 30484-30486, 188648, 188649, 08335-08340, 08346, 08347, 08352, 10359, 10361, 10362, 08331, 1-24.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 09550, 07318-07322, 07324, 07326-07328, 07331, 188648, 188649, 18103, 30484-30486, 30692-30694, 08336, 08352, 10359, 10361, 10362, 08331, 1-24. There are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 061231, 31368, 31369, 31380, 31381, 16306-16309, 18101, 18102, 05351-05356, 09550, 10358, 10360, 10363, 10364, 08332-08334, 10359, 10361, 10362, 74657.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 47 Folders 4-13 for negatives.
    - TFI, binder 1, 1990 (Box 20, Folders 2-3)
      Contains 3,700 mixed images; Rolls: 8132, 8133, 8136-8139, 8244-8251, 8302-8306, 37074-37081, 8364-8369, 4667, 8386-8391.
      Note: there are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 8238-8240, 8352, 8353 (note attached: "8/8/90 I've got TFI #8352, #8353 contacts –Rory.")
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 48 Folders 6-10 for negatives.
    - TFI, binder 2, 1990 (Box 20, Folders 4-6)
      Contains 3,700 mixed images; Rolls: 4666, 4668, 8404-8406, 8408-8413, 8425-8427, 8487-8489, 8506, 8507, 8659, 8610-8617, 8646-8661, 8663, 8729-8734.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 48 Folders 11-16 for negatives.
    - TFI, binder 3, (2 folders), 1989 (Box-folder 19-9, Box-folder 20-1)
      Contains 6,300 black and white images; Rolls: 11292, 11293, 11737, 11739, 11795-11797, 15573, 16336-16339, 18409-18411, 188649, 22347-22350, 23155-23157, 25692, 26942, 28979-28981, 27368, 28982-28984, 30147, 27-34, 8038-8049, 8053-8064, 8131-8139, 8237-8240.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 25692, 8132-8134, 8136-8139, 8237-8240. There are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 11738, 11793, 11798, 24069-24071, 24073, 24074, 30484-30486, 30692-30696.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 47 Folder 14 to Flat Box 48 Folder 5 for negatives.
    - TFI #1 (1 of 2) (Flat-box 78, Folder 10)
      30 black and white prints
    - TFI #1 (2 of 2) (Flat-box 78, Folder 11)
      31 black and white prints
    - TFI #2 (Flat-box 78, Folder 12)
    - TFI #3 (Flat-box 78, Folder 13)
      10 black and white prints
    - Trimble, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Contains 144 black and white images; Rolls: 235-239.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 48 Folder 17 for negatives.
    - United Technologies, 1995 (Box 20, Folders 8-9)
      Contains 812 mixed images; Rolls: 58013-58015, 58017-58034, 58098, 423 (selected prints only).
      Note: there are no contact sheets for the following roll: 423. Roll 58024 is incomplete, negatives 13-18 are missing.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 48 Folders 18-20 for negatives.
    - Voyager, 1991 (Box 20, Folders 10-11)
      Contains 1,000 black and white images; Rolls: 6912-6915, 6917-6933, 73899, 73901.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 6929. There are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 73898, 73900.
      See See Subseries 3, Flat Box 49 Folders 1-3 for negatives.
    - Wollongong, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      Contains 360 black and white images; Rolls: 103721-103732.
      See Subseries 3, Flat Box 49 Folder 4 for negatives.
  - Subseries 2. Photo Shoots
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject. Folders contain slides, contact sheets, prints and negatives; most include caption sheets and notes. Overall number of slides unspecified. Negatives have been removed and stored in flat boxes for preservation purposes and are OPEN to research. Many negatives do not correspond to contact sheets and are occasionally unnumbered. Not all rolls of negatives are complete.
    - ACA Joe (Box 21, Folder 1)
      35-mm slides: (1 sleeve)
    - ACA Joe (Flat-box 50, Folder 1)
      Negatives without contact sheets: 3 rolls: 357-359
    - Acrobat Cowgirls (Box 21, Folders 2-4)
      35-mm slides: (17 sleeves)
    - Adoption (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Miscellaneous prints: (11)
    - Adoption (Flat-box 50, Folder 6)
      Negatives: 7 rolls: C1-C7
    - AIDS (Box 21, Folder 6)
      35-mm slides: (8 sleeves)
    - AIDS (Flat-box 50, Folders 2-5)
      Negatives without contact sheets: rolls: 4980-4986, 749, 751, 29758, 647, 649-660, 261-265, 506-510, 782, 502-505
    - AIDS, Day in the Life of (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Contact sheets: (4 sheets)
    - AIDS, Day in the Life of (Flat-box 50, Folder 7)
      Negatives: 5 rolls: roll numbers not assigned
    - AIDS - Jim Ross - Gay Catholics (Box 21, Folder 8)
      35-mm slides: (6 sleeves)
    - AIDS - San Francisco (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - AIDS/Stress/Testing (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Contact sheets: (6 sheets)
    - AIDS/Stress/Testing (Flat-box 50, Folder 8)
      Negatives: 6 rolls: 21760, unnumbered
    - AIDS Project (Box 21, Folder 11)
      35-mm slides: (3 sleeves)
    - Aids Testing (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Airlift Africa (Box 22, Folders 1-10)
      35-mm slides: (66 sleeves)
    - Airlift Africa - Ethiopian Famine (Box 23, Folders 1-2)
      35-mm slides: (12 sleeves)
    - Airplanes (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Akagi, Doug (Box 23, Folder 4)
      35-mm slides: (5 sleeves)
    - Alderson, Sandy (General Manger, Oakland A's) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Alopecia Areata (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Alopecia Areata (Flat-box 50, Folder 9)
      Negatives without contact sheets: 2 rolls: 973, 974
    - Amazon/ Power to Heal (Box 23, Folders 7-10)
      35-mm slides: (30 sleeves)